Hi, I'm Rasheed. I'm the newest member of the
Robotics Cohort in the Atlanta AI and Robotics
Initiative in summer 2026. This summer, I've had
the opportunity to have hands-on experience
in hardware manufacturing, robotics, and just
old-fashioned programming as well. Across the
board, it's been great to have access to
resources like mentorship from cutting-edge
entrepreneurs
in the tech space and experienced professionals
in the corporate technology world as well from
companies like Waymo and Amazon. Also, and a
personal favorite part of the program for
me has been the ability to work with budding
scientists from starting from ages 14 and
up on robotics projects that interest us both
and allow us both to grow and learn together.
I think if you're interested in technology in
general, if you're interested in pursuing
mentorship or certification in technology, then
the Atlanta AI and Robotics Initiative
is something that can really jumpstart your
career and put you in the right mindset
to make a difference here in Atlanta, but also
in any room you walk into.